Yelena!
Yelena, c'mon!
Lunch will be over soon.
Why'd you bring us so far out?
Anya, over here!
I'm sorry.
Well done, Yelena.
Your first test is now complete.
Stay quiet, Valentina.
Completely quiet, no matter what you hear.
You promise me?
Did I do something wrong?
The man in town asked where we live.
He said he was your friend, so I told him.
Yes, well he was.
Remember I told you not to talk to anyone?
Yes, daddy. I'm so sorry.
It's okay. Just stay hidden for me.
You know...
I've been in this business a long time.
There's always someone like you,
smart, but cocky.
A hungry dog who already had
a bone in his mouth.
Let's have a drink, shall we?
You still think
you're getting away with this.
Don't worry,
I'll look out for your sweet Valentina.
Yelena, c'mon!
Lunch will be over soon.
Why'd you bring us so far out?
Anya, over here!
I'm sorry.
It's too late for that, friend.